http://www.kilroyscollege.ie/privacy.php

Courses
Leaving Certificate 2021BusinessChildcarePsychologyBeauty & HealthCreative & LeisureIT & Computer SkillsCareer PreparationFilm & MediaJunior Certificate
Kilroy's College website privacy notice
Updated: 24th May 2018
How we use your information
This privacy notice tells you what to expect when Kilroy's College collects personal information via our websites. Kilroy's College take their obligations regarding your personal information very seriously. This privacy notice applies to information we collect about:
people who purchase Kilroy's College products and services, e.g. courses
people who subscribe or register to receive information from Kilroy's College, e.g. course brochures and newsletters
people who participate in Kilroy's College research and surveys
people who enter competitions
people who provide feedback to Kilroy's College via our websites
job applicants
visitors to our website
If you are giving us your personal information while purchasing, registering, or subscribing to a service or product, then we will only use your information in order to provide you with that service or for closely related purposes.
Kilroy's College uses some carefully selected third parties to help us to deliver these services and products to you. However, they are only allowed to use your personal information to deliver the service or product you have purchased, registered or subscribed to. Some of our trusted third parties in supporting these services will transfer your information overseas, but we make sure that your information remains protected and secure.
We will keep your personal information relating to services or products purchased in line with our retention policy which ensures that we keep your details for no longer than is necessary. Your information will be kept in a secure environment and access to it will be restricted on a 'need to know' basis only.
When you purchase certain products and services from Kilroy's College we may send you confirmation emails; these may also include marketing which we consider may be of interest to you. We do our best to tailor this information so that it is useful to you, but if at any time you no longer wish to receive it, you can opt out by following the instructions that we will give you with each communication.
Access to personal information
Any individual can find out if we hold any personal information by making a 'subject access request' under the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003. If we do hold information about you we will:
give you a description of it
tell you why we were holding it
tell you who it could be disclosed to
let you have a copy of the information in a form that is clear and concise
To make a request to Kilroy's College for any personal information we may hold please put a request in writing using the contact details found at the end of this notice.
If we do hold information about you, you can ask us to correct any mistakes by contacting us using the contact details provided.
Complaints and queries
Kilroy's College strives to meet the highest standards when collecting and using personal information. For this reason, we take any complaints we receive about this very seriously. We therefore encourage people to bring it to our attention if they think our collection or use of personal information is unfair, misleading or inappropriate.
Disclosure of personal information
In the vast majority of cases we will not disclose your personal information to others unless we have previously gained your consent. However, there will be circumstances where we may disclose your personal information without your consent, e.g. where we are required by law to disclose information or where the information is required to prevent or detect a crime. In the case of all disclosures we will always ensure the disclosure is legitimate and proportionate for the purpose.
Privacy & Cookies
What are cookies?
Cookies are small text files which are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages. At Kilroy's College, we use cookies to understand how our sites are used. This allows us to improve your overall online experience. Some of the cookies that we use are necessary for some of our sites to work whilst other cookies are used to provide tailored advertising by trusted third parties. The cookies we and our third parties place on your computer do not collect personally identifiable information like your name, address or payment details. To find out more about cookies, please visit www.aboutcookies.org
The privacy of your information is extremely important to us and so we want to keep you well informed about cookies. We shall continue to work on initiatives in relation to recent cookie legislation to ensure you have the best experience when visiting our websites.
The different types of cookies we use
Kilroy's College use the following categories of cookies on our websites:
Strictly necessary: These cookies are essential for certain features of our websites to work for example when you make payments for courses. These cookies do not record identifiable personal information and we do not need your consent to place these cookies on your device. Without these cookies some services you have asked for cannot be provided.
Functionality: These cookies are used to provide services or to remember settings to enhance your visit - for example text size or other preferences. The information that these cookies collect is anonymous and does not enable us to track your browsing activity on other websites. By using our websites, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device.
Performance: These cookies are used to collect anonymous information about how you use our websites. This information is used to help us improve our websites and understand how effective our adverts are. In some case we use trusted third parties to collect this information for us, but they only use the information for the purposes explained. By using our websites, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device.
Targeting and advertising: These cookies are used by trusted third parties to deliver adverts that are more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. Information contained in these cookies is anonymous and doesn't contain your personal information. To find out more about cookies used for targeting and advertising follow www.youronlinechoices.com and www.networkadvertising.org or contact us at the address below for further information about the trusted third parties we use.
Managing cookies
If you'd prefer to restrict, block or delete cookies from Kilroy's College and our third party advertisers, or any other website, you can use your browser to do this. Each browser is different, so check the 'Help' menu of your own browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Please note that if you choose to disable all cookies we cannot guarantee the performance of our websites and some features may not work as expected.
Links to other websites
This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit.
Changes to this privacy notice
Kilroy's College keep our privacy notice under regular review and we will place any updates on this webpage. We reserve the right to modify this statement at any time. Each time you use this website you shall be bound by the then current Privacy Statement and accordingly you should review the Privacy Statement each time you visit the website. At the start of this privacy notice we will tell you when the Privacy Statement was last updated.
How to contact us
Data Protection Manager
Kilroy's College
Wentworth House
13 Eblana Villas
Dublin 2
D02 Y970
Ireland
This privacy notice does not provide exhaustive detail of all aspects of our collection and use of personal information. However, Kilroy's College are happy to provide any additional information or explanation needed. Please send any requests for this to the contact address above.
Data Protection Policy
Courses
Leaving Certificate 2021BusinessChildcarePsychologyBeauty & HealthCreative & LeisureIT & Computer SkillsCareer PreparationFilm & MediaJunior Certificate
Enrol Online
Select a courseAdult Psychology Advanced ECDL Army and Navy Recruitment
Avionics Beauty Therapy Book-keeping & Accounts Business Administration Business Management Business of Film with Kieran Corrigan Child Development QQI Level 6 Child Psychology Child Psychology QQI Level 6 Childcare Diploma Childhood Social, Legal and Health Studies QQI Level 6 CIW Advanced HTML5 and CSS3 Specialist CIW Data Analyst CIW Web Design CIW Web Security Clerical Officer Entrance Combined Child Care & Psychology Communication Skills CompTIA A+ CompTIA Network + Creative Writing Creative Writing (Junior) CV Preparation and Interview Techniques Digital Photography Dog Grooming Dressmaking Early Childhood Curriculum QQI Level 6 ECDL - New Version 6 English Literature Executive Officer Entrance Farm Accounting & Taxation Film & TV Production Filmmaking with John Boorman Fitness, Health and Nutrition Forensic Psychology & Criminology Freelance Journalism Future of TV and Cross-Platform Production Garda Recruitment Stage 1 Gardening General Education Studies Golf Psychology Junior Certificate English Junior Certificate Mathematics Keyboard & Typing Skills Leaving Certificate Accounting Leaving Certificate Biology Leaving Certificate Business Leaving Certificate Chemistry Leaving Certificate Economics Leaving Certificate English Leaving Certificate French Leaving Certificate Geography Leaving Certificate German Leaving Certificate History Leaving Certificate Irish Leaving Certificate Maths Leaving Certificate Physics Leaving Certificate Spanish Make-up Artist Managing Your Work Mature Nursing Midwifery Test Preparation Microsoft Access Microsoft Excel Microsoft Office Master Microsoft Outlook Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Word Nail Technician Paramedic Recruitment PC Repair & Upgrading Photography Prison Officer Recruitment Self-Employed Accounting & Taxation Smart Filmmaking Speak French Speak Spanish Sport Psychology Supervision in Early Childhood Care QQI Level 6 Visual Effects (VFX) with DNEG
ENROL NOW
Free Prospectus
Request your free Kilroy's College prospectus here.
REQUEST PROSPECTUS
Courses
Leaving Certificate 2021BusinessChildcarePsychologyBeauty & HealthCreative & LeisureIT & Computer SkillsCareer PreparationFilm & MediaJunior Certificate
Enrol Online
Select a courseAdult Psychology Advanced ECDL Army and Navy Recruitment
Avionics Beauty Therapy Book-keeping & Accounts Business Administration Business Management Business of Film with Kieran Corrigan Child Development QQI Level 6 Child Psychology Child Psychology QQI Level 6 Childcare Diploma Childhood Social, Legal and Health Studies QQI Level 6 CIW Advanced HTML5 and CSS3 Specialist CIW Data Analyst CIW Web Design CIW Web Security Clerical Officer Entrance Combined Child Care & Psychology Communication Skills CompTIA A+ CompTIA Network + Creative Writing Creative Writing (Junior) CV Preparation and Interview Techniques Digital Photography Dog Grooming Dressmaking Early Childhood Curriculum QQI Level 6 ECDL - New Version 6 English Literature Executive Officer Entrance Farm Accounting & Taxation Film & TV Production Filmmaking with John Boorman Fitness, Health and Nutrition Forensic Psychology & Criminology Freelance Journalism Future of TV and Cross-Platform Production Garda Recruitment Stage 1 Gardening General Education Studies Golf Psychology Junior Certificate English Junior Certificate Mathematics Keyboard & Typing Skills Leaving Certificate Accounting Leaving Certificate Biology Leaving Certificate Business Leaving Certificate Chemistry Leaving Certificate Economics Leaving Certificate English Leaving Certificate French Leaving Certificate Geography Leaving Certificate German Leaving Certificate History Leaving Certificate Irish Leaving Certificate Maths Leaving Certificate Physics Leaving Certificate Spanish Make-up Artist Managing Your Work Mature Nursing Midwifery Test Preparation Microsoft Access Microsoft Excel Microsoft Office Master Microsoft Outlook Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Word Nail Technician Paramedic Recruitment PC Repair & Upgrading Photography Prison Officer Recruitment Self-Employed Accounting & Taxation Smart Filmmaking Speak French Speak Spanish Sport Psychology Supervision in Early Childhood Care QQI Level 6 Visual Effects (VFX) with DNEG
ENROL NOW
Free Prospectus
Request your free Kilroy's College prospectus here.
REQUEST PROSPECTUS
Useful Links
Courses
Current Offers
Free Prospectus
Accreditation
E-Learning Login
How it Works
Contact Details
Kilroy's College,
Wentworth House,
Grand Canal Street,
Dublin 2,
D02 Y970
Ireland
Ph: 1850 700 700 (24 hrs)
Ph: 01 639 4660
Fax: 01 662 0539
Email: info@kilroyscollege.ie
Leading Irish provider of affordable, accessible and accredited distance learning courses anywhere in the world since 1932.
© Copyright Kilroy's College 2020
This site uses cookies to provide you with an optimal user experience. By continuing to use this site, you consent to the use of cookies in accordance with our cookie policy. Accept
